techgenix.com 2019-07-31

# Privacy Policy - TechGenix

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](http://g.ezoic.net/privacy/techgenix.com).  

## Introduction

TechGenix Limited (“TechGenix” or “We”) are committed to fair information practices and we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect certain information during your visits to our websites and the use of our services to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users. We may also ask you to provide personal information to enable us to give you access to some parts of our web sites and use of our services. We will not disclose your personal information to any person outside our organisation except as described in this Privacy Policy.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) disclosing our practices regarding your information. This Privacy Policy describes what personal identifying information is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, how you can correct any inaccuracies in your information and the options you have with regard to how your personal information is used.

This Privacy Policy applies to information that we obtain from users interacting with TechGenix and its websites and services. By accessing the TechGenix website at [www.techgenix.com](http://www.techgenix.com/), including all related pages and sub-domains (“the Websites”) and using any services offered by TechGenix (collectively the “Services”) you are accepting and agreeing to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy please do not use the Websites or Services. This Privacy Policy may be updated and revised from time to time and you are deemed to have accepted the most current version each time you use our Websites. Please take the time to read this Privacy Policy.

## Personal Information provided or collected by us

In general you can visit our Websites without providing any personal information. However, if users register to obtain access to some parts of our Websites or Services we may request that you voluntarily supply us with certain personal information. Some of the information requested will be required to use the Websites or Services and some may be optional. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including but not limited to a first and last name, company name, e-mail address, telephone number, physical address, billing information and other such information needed to provide the Services that you request. Personal Information does not include aggregate or non-personally identifiable information.

TechGenix may collect your personal information in the following ways: (i) when you register to use our Websites and Services (ii) when you sign up to receive our newsletters (iii) when you register for an event or webinar, (iv) when you participate in our surveys or questionnaires (v) when you enter into any promotions, contests or sweepstakes or (vi) when you correspond with us.

## Non- Personal Information Collected By Us

As you navigate through our Websites and Services certain anonymous information may be collected automatically using various technologies such as web server logs, cookies and web beacons as described below. Aggregate information is information that we collect about a group or category of users or services that is not personally identifiable. We use this aggregate and other non-personal information to administer, maintain and improve our Websites and Services. This information can be used for internal/external marketing purposes to analyze trends and summarize statistics. It can also provide information about interests and preferences of our users which enables us to target Services that you may find helpful and informative. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose.

  * _Web server logs_. When you visit our Websites or use our Services, we may track information related to website usage to administer the Websites and Services and analyze their usage. Examples of information we may collect includes your internet protocol address, what type of browser or computer you use, the number of links you click within the Website, the state or country from which you accessed the Website, the date and time of your visit, the name of your internet services provider, the last page you viewed before visiting our Website, and the pages you viewed on the Website.
  * _Cookies & beacons_. If your browser allows it, our Websites and Services use cookies, which are small text files which your computer creates or modifies on instruction of the page opened in your browser. These cookies are used to save your preferences and login information and display personalized content to maximize the performance of our Websites and Services. If you register to use our Services or continue to use our Websites you agree to our use of cookies. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies however, please note that certain features of the Websites or Services may not be available once cookies are disabled.

Furthermore, if your browser allows it, third party cookies may be used for adverts placed on the pages of our Websites. The third-party advertising companies which serve ads when you visit our Websites may use information about your visits to our Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This information is neither controlled nor used by us and is subject to the privacy policies of the third parties concerned. Specifically, if your browser allows it, where Google adverts are placed on the pages of our Websites, Google will attempt to use one or more cookies called 'DoubleClick DART cookie' to serve ads based on your visit to our Websites and to other sites on the Internet. You can find more information, and opt out of Google advertising cookies, at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

Furthermore, where third party ads, and specifically Google adverts are placed on the pages of our Websites, a web beacon may be included. A web beacon is a small and unnoticable image served by the third party advertiser in order to collect information from your browser to compile aggregated statistics regarding our Websites and Services. If javascript is not enabled in your browser, or if you use certain ad-blockers, you may not see adverts and therefore you may not be aware that ads are being served.

Our Websites and Services may contain links to other third party sites that are not owned or controlled by TechGenix. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Once you have left our Websites you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

## Use Of And Access To Information

TechGenix uses your personal information for several general purposes. We may use your personal information to (i) provide and improve our Websites and Services for which you have registered (ii) administer your use of the Websites and Services (iii) provide customer support and assistance (iv) carry out our contractual obligations entered into between you and us (v) respond to requests or correspondence from you (vi) communicate special offers, promotions and events to you (vii) enable you to post on our blog forum and (viii) allow us to keep you posted on TechGenix’s latest announcements.

From time to time we may also use your personal information to send you important notices such as communications about the Websites, Services, your subscription, renewals, technical issues, security announcements or changes to our terms or policies.

Additionally, we may also use personal information you provide to contact you regarding products, services, upcoming events and offers both from ourselves and third parties that we believe you may find of interest. You may elect to opt-out of receiving marketing or promotional communication from us at any time by following the instructions contained within the e-mail or by sending a request to [[email protected]](http://techgenix.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0673687573647565746f6463467263656e6163686f7e2865696b)[.](http://www.techgenix.com/privacy-policy.htm#)

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may use and disclose aggregate information and other non-personally identifiable information for various purposes at our sole discretion in an effort to customize or enhance the content and advertising of our Websites and Services. Except as described in this Privacy Policy we will not disclose your personal information that we collect to third parties without your consent.

From time to time we may disclose your personal information to the following third parties where necessary:

  * Members of the TechGenix group of companies for purposes described in this Privacy Policy. These affiliated companies may disclose personal information and other information that we disclose to them in accordance with their privacy policies and procedures.
  * Service providers and contractors who perform services on our behalf for purposes such as payment processing, analyzing data, marketing assistance or customer service. We limit the personal information that is provided to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions and we require them to agree to maintain strict confidentiality of such personal information.
  * Strategic partners that work with Techgenix to provide services or to help us market to customers. These third parties may use such personal information and other information to contact you either on our behalf or for their own account about products, services or offers that we believe are important to you or your business. If you do not wish to us to share your personal information with affiliated third parties for promotional purposes you can opt-out by sending us an email or following the instructions given in the email you receive.
  * If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction.
  * For any other purpose that we may disclose to you at the point at which we request your personal information and pursuant to your consent.

## Compliance with Legal Process

We may be required to disclose your personal information and/or information with respect to your use of our Websites, products and services if required by subpoena or other legal process or requirement or if we reasonably believe that such disclosure is necessary (i) to investigate, prevent or take action with respect to suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies, (ii) to protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury, (iii) prevent fraud or abuse of our Websites or infringement of our intellectual property rights in our products and services, (iv) to enforce our terms of use or your agreements with us, or (v) to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations.

## Your choices

If you are a registered user of our Websites or Services and you do not want to be on our mailing list you can opt-out of receiving these communications at any point by sending an email to: [unsubscr[email protected]](http://techgenix.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#780d160b0d1a0b1b0a111a1d380c1d1b101f1d161100561b1715). You can also stop receiving marketing communications by following the instructions in the email you receive. These choices do not apply to the receipt of mandatory Website or Services communications that are considered part of the Services, including information about your subscription, renewals, technical issues, security announcements or changes to our terms or policies. Please be aware that if you opt-out of receiving commercial e-mail from us, it may take up to ten business days for us to process your opt-out request and you may receive commercial email from us during that period.

## Access to Information

You have the right to request access to the information we have on you. You can do this by sending a message through our contact page at <http://www.techgenix.com/contact> or by sending an email to [[email protected]](http://techgenix.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#264f484049665243454e4143484f5e0845494b).

We will make sure to provide you with a copy of the data we have about you within a reasonable timeframe from the time of your request. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. We will fulfill your request by sending your copy electronically. For any subsequent access requests, we may charge an administrative fee.

## Updates And Corrections

If you wish to update or correct your personal information, please use our contact page at <http://techgenix.com/contact/> to send us a message clearly stating which changes you wish to make.

## Data Retention

We will keep and use your data as described in this Privacy Policy for (i) as long as your account is in use, is open, or is active; (ii) as long as is necessary to comply with any tax, legal, and/or other regulatory requirements; and (iii) to protect and defend against potential legal claims.

## Right to be Forgotten

TechGenix is committed to taking reasonable steps to ensure that any personal information removal requests be done within a reasonable timeframe. However, if comments have been made publicly by posting on our forums, blogs, or have made available to third parties yourself, it has been made public record and may be beyond what we are capable of removing. TechGenix will do everything possible to erase your personal information if you withdraw your consent (opt out) from receiving information from us and request the right of removal of your personal data and your account to be terminated. We will not be able to erase all of your personal information if it is technically impossible due to limitations to existing technology, or for legal reasons (TechGenix is mandated by local law to keep the personal information).

## Security and Transfer

We use administrative, organizational, technical and physical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information we collect. Although we use industry standard security measures, the Internet is not a 100% secure environment and we cannot, and do not, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit or store using the Websites. There is no guarantee that your information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards and we are not responsible for third party circumvention of your privacy settings or our security measures. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information and for controlling access to your account. If any data security breach occurs and it may impact your personal information, you will be notified as soon as possible once the breach has been determined.

We may transfer the personal information we obtain to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. The information that we collect from our users may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the EEA. It may also be processes by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal information you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

## Other Information Supplied By You

In some parts of our Websites (such as chat rooms, forums, message boards or news groups) you can submit or contribute information. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Do not disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential. TechGenix will not be responsible in the event that you disclose personal or confidential information in your posts or during any other communication with other site users.

## External Websites

Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have. You should use caution and review the privacy policies of any web sites, services or third party providers that you visit from our Websites or our products to learn more about their information practices, which may be significantly different from ours.

## Children

Children are not eligible to use our Websites and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use our Websites. Our Websites are not directed to children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [[email protected]](http://techgenix.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1c69726f697e6f7f6e757e795c68797f747b79727564327f7371). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our Websites. You should check this page occasionally to review any changes. We will provide notice of any changes by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Websites. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed with respect to any changes to this Privacy Policy. Using our Websites or continuing to provide personal information to us after a notice of changes has been sent to you or published on our Websites shall constitute consent to the changed terms and practices. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all personal information you have provided to us.

## Controller of Personal Information

The Data Controller for the Websites and Services is TechGenix Ltd.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to: [[email protected]](http://techgenix.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#224b4c444d625647414a45474c4b5a0c414d4f0c)

_Privacy Policy last updated on May 29, 2018_
